A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of XXX: Correspondence, 1990-1994.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Policy Office Correspondence of XXX,
1990-1994.
The Library of Virginia
35539
Virginia. Governor (1990-1994: XXX).
XX cu. ft. (XX boxes)
Administrative Information
Arranged by series.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 35539 was transferred by Gov. Lawrence Douglas Wilder, October 31, 1996.
Historical Information
XX
XX
Scope and Content
XX
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1990-1994
Contents List
- Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1990-1994.
  - Secretary of Administration.
    - General correspondence (Porfiri), 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence (McFarlane), 1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence, 1992 Jan-Feb. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - General correspondence, 1992 Mar-May. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - General correspondence, 1992 June-July. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - General correspondence, 1992 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - General correspondence, 1992 Sep-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - General correspondence, 1993 Jan-May. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence, 1993 June-July. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence, 1993 Aug-Nov. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Abbreviation of state agency names, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Appointment of legal holidays, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Beyer Commission - Federal Schedule A Program, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Budget, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Capital outlay process, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Concerned contractors - Jackson contract, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Decision brief - Psychiatrists, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Early retirement, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Federal Audit of Internal Service Funds, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Grievance procedures, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Grigsby Brandford and Co., 1993. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Madison Building, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Self-administration of Workers' Commpensation language, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - State employee health benefits, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - State Recruitment Policies - State Police, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Telecommuting, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Use of state facilities, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Use of state facilities, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Port Authority - Police, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Compensation Board, 1990-1992. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Elections, State Board of: Board, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Elections, State Board of: Certificate of Election for U.S. Senate, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Elections, State Board of: Felon registration, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Elections, State Board of: National Voter Registration / Motor Voter, undated. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Elections, State Board of: Norfolk election district, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Elections, State Board of: Potential violations of election laws (Manassas), 1990. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Elections, State Board of: Voter registration, 1990-1993. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1990-1993. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Street Project, 1988. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project, 1991-1993. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project, 1993 Jan-Aug. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project, 1993 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project, 1993 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project, 1993 Nov-Dec. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project - Background information (1970s), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project - McFarlane Report, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project - McFarlane Report, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project - Miscellaneous, 1993, undated. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project - Original plans, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - General Services, Dept. of: 900 E. Main Project - Original plans, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Asbestos issues briefing, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Capital Outlay Progress Reports, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Commonwealth Park Suites Hotel, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Demolition, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Jefferson Building / Virginia State Library, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Fisher Deed, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Forbes property, 1990. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Master Plan and Study Report - Capitol Square Complex and Broad Street Station Site (v. I), 1993. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Master Plan and Study Report - Capital Square Complex and Broad Street Station Site (v. II), 1993. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Risk Management, 1991-1993. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Risk Management, 1991-1993. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Surplus Property, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - General Services, Dept. of: Water Chemistry, Inc., 1990-1991. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Human Rights, Council on, 1990-1993. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of, 1990-1993. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of: Agency phone charges, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of: Notice of protest by Bell Atlantic to IBM, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Information Technology, Dept of: Oracle, 1991. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Information Management, Council on, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Local Government, Commission on, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Local Government, Commission on, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Local Government, Commission on: Executive Assessment of Local Government Mandates, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1990. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of: Early Retirement Replacement Policy, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of: Fair Labor Standards Act, 1991. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of: Fair Labor Standards Act, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of: Health benefits, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of: Layoff Policy, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of: Leave share, 1990-1991. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Personnel and Training, Dept. of: Sexual Harassment Policy, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Affairs, Dept. of:, 1990-1991. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Veterans Affairs, Dept. of: Veterans Home, 1990-1991. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Retirement System, 1990. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Retirement System, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Retirement System, 1992. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Retirement System, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Benefit supplements, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Board guidelines, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Board meeting, 1992 Nov 19. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Component Unit Financial Reports, 1990-1991. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Counsel for VRS real estate ventures, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Early Retirement Program, 1990. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Emerging Money Managers, 1991-1992. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Equity Program / Investments, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Legislative Studies, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Little v. VRS, 1990-1993. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Retirement System: New England Mutual Insurance and Copley Real Estate, 1993. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Retirement System: Presentation to House Appropriations Committee, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Retirement System: RFP investment, 1990-1991. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Retirement System: RFP investment, 1992-1993. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Retirement System: RFP investment, 1993. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Retirement System: RFP investment, 1993 Nov. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Retirement System: RFP investment - JLARC Report, 1993 Oct. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Retirement System: RFP investment - JLARC Report, 199. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Retirement System: RFP investment - Special Report of the Attorney General, 1992. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Retirement System: RFP investment - Wilder v. Terry (Supreme Court of Virginia), 1992. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development.
    - General correspondence, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence, 1991 Jan-Sept. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence, 1991 Oct. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence, 1991 Nov-Dec. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence, 1992 Jan-Mar. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence, 1992 Apr-Sept. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence, 1992 Oct-Nov. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence, 1993 Jan-Feb. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence, 1993 Mar-Nov. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Ambassador Yoshio Hatano, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - American Home Products (A.H. Robins), 1991. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Angola, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Avian influenza, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Biotech Research Act, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Bond issues - Articles of Incorporation and Bylaws (Bond Foundation), 1992. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Chesapeake Port Authority, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Clinch Valley College Visitors Center, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Coal field jobs, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Coal industry retiree health, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Coal mining at Buchanan County Correctional Facility, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Colorado Act, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Commissioning of the USS George Washington, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Containarized cargo, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Defense Conversion - Base closures, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Defense Conversion - Defense cutbacks, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Defense Conversion - Dept. of Defense, 1992. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Defense Conversion - FAST Ships, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Defense Conversion - Governor's Conference on, 1993. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Disaster Relief - Drought (Fauquier and Clarke), 1991. (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Dredging - Southern Branch of the Elizabeth River, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Economic Development goals, undated. (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Economic Recovery Commission, 1991. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Energy Policy (DMME), 1991. (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Final Report of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994 Jan. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Final Report of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994 Jan. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Ford Foundation, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Forest wardens, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Funding for Employment Services, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - GATT, 1991-1992. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - General Dynamics, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Ghana Trade Delegation, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Guidelines for Review of Regulations by the Secretary of Economic Development, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Hadson Power 12 - Altavista, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Hardwood Chipping Study, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Hawaii golf course development, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Haysi Dam, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Haysi Dam, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Haysi Dam, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Health Provider Tax Campaign, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Hershey Food Project, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Hoffman-Laroche, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Hospitality packs for Congressional Democratic Caucus, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Household International, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Housing and Community Development, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Hughes Training, Inc., 1991. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - INC Council of Growing Companies, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Industrial members of the Air Pollution Control Board, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Interstate Oil Compact Commission, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Japan / Southeast U.S. Association, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Jurisdiction of Norfolk Southern, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Labor-Industry Coalition for International Trade (LICIT), 1991. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Lake Gaston, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Lease DED, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Lego World, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - LJs Coal Corp., 1991. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Long-Range Economic Development Plan, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Longworth, Jim, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Low Income Housing Tax Credit, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Main Street Designation (DHCD), 1992. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Mass layoff at Credit Card Services Corp., 1990. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - MCI, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - McQuinn, Delores, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Meadowview Treatment Plant, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Mine Safety and Health Administration - Elimination of State Grant Mind Training, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Miner's health care benefits, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Mobil Oil, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Motor fuels laws, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Multi-family Housing Bonds (VHDA), 1992. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Multi-family Housing Bonds (VHDA), 1992-1993. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Namibia, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - New England Defense Contractors survey, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Northern Virginia Economic Forum, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Northern Virginia Economic Forum - Meeting, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Outstanding issues for the Governor's review, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Overall Authority Consolidation, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Passports, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Phoenix Recycling Corp. - Community Block Grant, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Port Tonnage (VPA), 1992. (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Press activities, 1991. (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Proposed federal increase on excise tax for cigarettes, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Real Estate Appraiser Board - Report to trust, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Richmond v. Croson, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Richmond Shafts - FY89 Projects, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Rural Development - Strategic Plan for Rural Development, 1991. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Rural Development - Rural Development Summit, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Rural Development - Virginia Economic Development Corp. (VEDCORP), 1990. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Rural Development - Virginia Economic Development Corp. (VEDCORP) - Breakfast, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Rural Development - Virginia Economic Development Corp. (VEDCORP), 1991. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Rural Development - Virginia Economic Development Corp. (VEDCORP), 1991. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Rural Development - Virginia Economic Development Corp. (VEDCORP), 1992. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Rural Development - Virginia Economic Development Corp. (VEDCORP) - Proxy, 1992. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Rural Development, Center on, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Sisisky - Subcommittee hearing, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Slant drilling (oil or gas) - Tidewater, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Southwest Virginia legislators, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - State Allocation of Private Activity Bond Authority, 1992. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Tourism in Western Virginia, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Trade Missions, 1990-1991. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Transfer of Bond Allocation to Virginia Housing Development Authority (VHDA), 1992. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Transfer of federal collection of royalty on mineral leases, 1992. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Unemployment insurance - Illegal drug control, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Unemployment rate, 1991 Dec. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - United Airlines, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - United Airlines, 1991 Jan. (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - United Airlines, 1991 Feb. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - United Airlines, 1991 Mar. (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - United Airlines, 1991 Apr-Sept. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - United Airlines - Legal analysis, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - United Airlines - Gateways, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - United Airlines - Meeting, 1990 Oct 15. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - United Airlines - Proposals, 1990-1991. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - United Maintenance and Operations Center for Recruitment, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), 1992. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Vance, Leonard (Clean Air Act), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Chamber's Report to Top Management luncheon, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Energy Guard, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Horse Racing Facility, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Virginia - Japan Golf Tournament, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Power negotiations with IBEW (strike), 1992. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Virginia's Facts and Figures publication, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Virginia's largest employers, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Vista Woods (Thompson, Gary), 1991. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - VSBFA - Industrial Development Bond Program, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Used Oil Regulatory Program, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Wakefield tire fire, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Wall, John (HUD), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Washington Capitals, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Welcome Centers, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - World Trade, Virginia Conference on, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - World Trade lease, 1991. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1990-1993. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Dept. of: Virginia Agricultural Development Authority, 1990-1991. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Commerce, Dept. of, 1990-1992. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Commerce, Dept. of: Cosmetology, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of, 1992-1993. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of: An Inside View of the Dept. of Economic Development, undated. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1990-1992. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Block Grant Program, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of: Low Income Housing Tax Credits, 1990-1991. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers Board, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1990 Jan-Mar. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1990 Oct-Dec. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of: Energy Conservation and Efficiency Plan, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of: Lee County mine accident, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of: Virginia Energy Plan, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1991-1992. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of: Contracting Policy, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of: Female and Minority Owned Investment Manager Database (A-H), 1990. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of: Female and Minority Owned Investement Manager Database (I-Z), 1990. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of: Minority contracting - Savings and Loan bailout, 1991. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Racing Commission, Virginia, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Racing Commission, Virginia, 1991-1993. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Employment Commission, 1990-1991. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Employment Commission: Aptitude tests (GATB), 1990. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Employment Commission: Virginia Trust Fund and Unemployment Insurance Workload, 1990-1993. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1991. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Port Authority, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Port Authority, 1991-1993. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Port Authority - Bonds, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Port Authority - Craney Island, 1990-1991. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education.
    - General correspondence, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence, 1992. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Council for Public Service (UVA) - Carl Stenburg request (SCHEV), 1991. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Council of Presidents - Members, 1990. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Disparity in Education, 1991-1992. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Disparity in Education, 1991 Dec. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Disparity in Education, 1992. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Disparity in Education - Lawsuits, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Disparity in Education - Lawsuits, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Divestment, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Dropout prevention, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Education, Board of - Speech (Dyke), 1991. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Elected school boards, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Funding - Private school education, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - GMU and GWU Indemnity, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Higher education desegregation, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Intercollegiate athletics, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Lunenburg - EPA issues, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Medical College of Virginia (MCV), 1993. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Minority scholarships, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Monitoring and Advisory Committee, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Outcome Accountability Project, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Outcome-based Education, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Outstanding Faculty Award Program, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Partnerships for Excellence, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Race exclusive scholarships, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Salary supplements for presidents, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - School safety / Gun control, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Speech - Superintendent's Conference (Dyke), 1991. (Box 23, Folder 22)